Finding Aid for James B. Griffin Papers 1922-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence, 1930-1975
  - Ledbetter, Robert E., 1969-1975 (Box 14)
  - Lee, Gilbert L., Jr., 1953-1954 (Box 14)
  - Lee, Thomas E., 1948-1959 (Box 14)
  - Leechman, Douglas, 1948-1952 (Box 14)
  - Lehman, Edward J., 1970-1975 (Box 14)
  - Lehmer, Donald J., 1948-1964 (Box 14)
  - Lemley, Harry J., 1936-1948 (Box 14)
  - Leonard, Justin W., 1955-1958 (Box 14)
  - Leslie, Vernon, 1952-1955 (Box 14)
  - Lessa, William A., 1952-1959 (Box 14)
  - Leverette, Bland K., 1972-1975 (Box 14)
  - Lewis, Ralph, 1968-1975 (Box 14)
  - Lewis, T.M.N., 1935-1975; 1 folders (Box 14)
    (1 of 2 folders)
  - Lewis, T.M.N., 1935-1975; 1 folders (Box 15)
    (2 of 2 folders)
  - Lieban, Richard W., 1966-1972 (Box 15)
  - Lilly, Eli, 1934-1977; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Lingelbach, William E., 1947-1948 (Box 15)
  - Linn, Robert M., 1961-1962 (Box 15)
  - Linne, Sigvald, 1935-1962 (Box 15)
  - Linton, Ralph, 1934-1948 (Box 15)
  - Lipe, William D., 1969-1974 (Box 15)
  - Lister, Robert H., 1948-1971 (Box 15)
  - Logan, Wilfred D., 1949-1974 (Box 15)
  - Lpez, Julius, 1956-1957 (Box 15)
  - Lorenzo, Jos Luis, 1956-1968 (Box 15)
  - Lothrup, S.K., 1948-1959 (Box 15)
  - Lottinville, Savoie, 1948-1960 (Box 15)
  - Lovis, William, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
  - Lozar, Rajko, 1956-1957 (Box 15)
  - Lucy, Charles L., 1947-1954 (Box 15)
  - Luedtke, Barbara, 1971-1974 (Box 15)
  - Lurie, Nancy, 1956-1974 (Box 15)
  - Lynch, Thomas F., 1974-1975 (Box 15)
  - La -- Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Le -- Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Li -- Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Lo to Lu -- Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - MacCord, Howard A., 1940-1974 (Box 15)
  - Macgowan, E.S., 1943-1949 (Box 15)
  - MacNeish, Richard S., 1941-1976; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Maher, Robert F., 1958-1964 (Box 15)
  - Malagon, Javier, 1952-1955 (Box 15)
  - Malkin, Borys, 1958-1967 (Box 15)
  - Mallory, Marjorie O., 1956 (Box 15)
    (re: Harlan I. Smith Manuscripts)
  - Malouf, Richard T., 1967-1975 (Box 15)
  - Mango, Susan A., 1975 (Box 15)
  - Manson, Carl, 1942-1956 (Box 15)
  - Margain, Carlos R., 1947-1952 (Box 15)
  - Marquina, Ignacio, 1946-1972 (Box 15)
  - Marshall, Byron C., 1953-1957 (Box 15)
  - Marshall, Richard A., 1953-1974 (Box 15)
  - Martin, Helen M., 1957-1958 (Box 16)
  - Martin, Paul S., 1933-1969 (Box 16)
  - Martnez; del Ro, Don Pablo, 1945-1959 (Box 16)
  - Mason, J. Alden, 1931-1960 (Box 16)
  - Mason, Ronald J., 1955-1973 (Box 16)
  - Masters, William, 1953 (Box 16)
  - Matson, Frederick R., 1934-1975 (Box 16)
  - Mattes, Merrill J., 1950-1952 (Box 16)
  - Maxwell, Moreau, 1947-1975 (Box 16)
  - Mayer-Oakes, William J., 1949-1968; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - McAllister, J. Gilbert, 1940-1947 (Box 16)
  - McBeth, Donald, 1951-1959 (Box 16)
  - McCartney, Allen P., 1963-1967 (Box 16)
  - McClurkan, Burney B., 1966-1974 (Box 16)
  - McCown, B.E., 1938-1959 (Box 16)
  - McCready, Norman L., 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - McGahey, Samuel O., 1969-1970 (Box 16)
  - McGimsey, Charles R., III, 1958-1975 (Box 16)
  - McGregor, John C., 1934-1975; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - McHugh, William P., 1972-1975 (Box 16)
  - McIlwrath, T.F., 1938-1960 (Box 16)
  - McIntire, William G., 1953-1958 (Box 16)
  - McKenzie, Douglas H., 1964-1973 (Box 16)
  - McKern, William C., 1933-1974; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - McKinley, Daniel, 1951-1969 (Box 16)
  - McKusick, Marshall, 1960-1975 (Box 16)
  - McMichael, Edward V., 1953-1967 (Box 16)
  - McMillan, R. Bruce, 1966-1975 (Box 16)
  - McNutt, Charles H., 1955-1975 (Box 16)
  - McPherron, Alan, 1959-1970 (Box 16)
  - McPherson, H.R., 1944-1965 (Box 16)
  - McPherson, Ian N., 1960-1962 (Box 16)
  - Mead, Margaret, 1956 (Box 16)
  - Meggers, Betty Evans, 1944-1947 (Box 16)
    (see also Evans, Clifford and Betty)
  - Meggitt, Mervyn, 1967-1974 (Box 16)
  - Meighan, Clement, 1955-1968 (Box 16)
  - Meleen, E.E., 1941-1948 (Box 16)
  - Menendes Amor, Josefa, 1957-1959 (Box 16)
  - Merrill, Robert H., 1945-1948 (Box 16)
  - Merwin, Bruce, 1934-1937 (Box 16)
  - Michael, Henry N., 1962-1968 (Box 16)
  - Michels, Joseph W., 1967-1969 (Box 16)
  - Michigan (University of) Press, 1953-1956 (Box 16)
  - Milisauskas, Sarunas, 1964-1975 (Box 16)
  - Miller, Carl F., 1950-1959 (Box 16)
  - Miller, William G., 1955-1968 (Box 16)
  - Millon, Ren, 1953-1970 (Box 16)
  - Miner, Horace, 1934-1971 (Box 16)
  - Mintz, Rene, 1956-1958 (Box 17)
  - Mitchell, Barry M., 1967-1970 (Box 17)
  - Moberg, Carl-Axel, 1958-1975 (Box 17)
  - Mochon, Marion, 1971-1975 (Box 17)
  - Moll, Harold W., 1957-1964 (Box 17)
  - Mook, Maurice, 1936-1948 (Box 17)
  - Moorehead, Warren K., 1935-1938 (Box 17)
  - Morgan, Richard G.
    - Correspondence, 1933-1970; 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Morgan Case, 1948 (Box 17)
      (re: dismissal from Ohio State Museum)
  - Morrell, L. Ross, 1967-1969 (Box 17)
  - Morris, Ben J., 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - Morris, Earl H., 1944-1953 (Box 17)
  - Morse, Dan F., 1955-1975; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Moser, Chris L., 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Movius, Hallam L., 1949-1969 (Box 17)
  - Mrozoski, Vincent R., 1957-1959 (Box 17)
  - Mulloy, William, 1940-1965 (Box 17)
  - Multiplex, 1950-1955 (Box 17)
  - Munson, Patrick J., 1963-1975 (Box 17)
  - Murdock, George P., 1941-1971 (Box 17)
  - Murphy, James L., 1964-1973 (Box 17)
  - Museum of Anthropology Directorship, 1943-1945 (Box 17)
  - Myers, Oliver H., 1958-1966 (Box 17)
  - Ma - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Mc - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - Me - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - Me to Mg - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - Mi - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Mo - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Mu to My - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Nakayam, Eiji, 1950-1956 (Box 18)
  - Nash, Charles H., 1936-1968 (Box 18)
  - Nash, Philleo, 1938-1939 (Box 18)
  - National Park Service, 1950-1955 (Box 18)
  - National Science Foundation, 1955-1974 (Box 18)
  - Neill, O.J., 1953-1958 (Box 18)
  - Neitzel, Robert S. (Stuart), 1936-1971 (Box 18)
  - Nelson, Cynthia, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Nelson, N.C., 1933-1947 (Box 18)
  - Nelson, Sarah, 1970-1974 (Box 18)
  - Nemec, Thomas, 1961-1967 (Box 18)
  - Nesbitt, Paul H., 1938-1975 (Box 18)
  - Neuman, Robert W., 1958-1975 (Box 18)
  - Neumann, Georg K., 1936-1970 (Box 18)
  - Newcomb, W.W., 1953-1972 (Box 18)
  - Newell, Perry, 1941-1942 (Box 18)
  - Newman, Marshall T., 1949-1952 (Box 18)
  - Nicholson, H.B., 1953-1959 (Box 18)
  - Noguera, Eduardo, 1943-1975 (Box 18)
  - Norbeck, Edward, 1951-1973 (Box 18)
  - Norona, Delf, 1950-1953 (Box 18)
  - Na to Ne - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Ni to Ny - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - O'Brien, Patricia J., 1967-1974 (Box 18)
  - Ochsner, Eugene E., 1970-1972 (Box 18)
  - Odegaard, Charles E., 1954-1958 (Box 18)
  - Oehler, Charles, 1947-1974 (Box 18)
  - Olafson, Sigfus, 1953-1972 (Box 18)
  - Omwake, H. Geiger, 1949-1966 (Box 18)
  - Orr, Ellison, 1947 (Box 18)
  - Orr, Kenneth G., 1945-1966 (Box 18)
  - Orr, Phil C., 1951-1963 (Box 18)
  - Osborne, Douglas, 1941-1965 (Box 18)
  - Osgood, Cornelius, 1940-1973 (Box 18)
  - Osmundsen, Lita, 1965-1975 (Box 18)
  - Oswalt, Wendell, 1953-1961 (Box 18)
  - Over, W.H., 1940-1948 (Box 18)
  - Owen, Marion, 1958-1960 (Box 18)
  - O'B to Ol -- Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - On to Ox -- Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Paddock, John, 1959-1966 (Box 19)
  - Palerm, Angel, 1955-1959 (Box 19)
  - Pan American Institute of Geography and History, 1954-1955 (Box 19)
  - Papworth, Mark, 1958-1971 (Box 19)
  - Parchert, Karl G., 1953-1964 (Box 19)
  - Parmalee, Paul W., 1957-1972 (Box 19)
  - Parsons, Jeffrey R., 1961-1975 (Box 19)
  - Parsons, John C., 1959-1968 (Box 19)
  - Parsons, Lee A., 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Peacock, Douglas, 1960-1970 (Box 19)
  - Peebles, Christopher, 1969-1974 (Box 19)
  - Peets, Orville H., 1953-1961 (Box 19)
  - Peithmann, Irvin, 1938-1953 (Box 19)
  - Pennak, Robert W., 1959-1961 (Box 19)
  - Pericot Garca, Luis, 1952-1958 (Box 19)
  - Perino, Gregory H., 1948-1975; 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Perrot, Jean, 1958-1970 (Box 19)
  - Personnel Office, 1953 (Box 19)
  - Peru, Don, 1958-1960 (Box 19)
  - Peske, G. Richard, 1961-1966 (Box 19)
  - Peters, Ralph W., 1947-1948 (Box 19)
  - Petersen, Eugene T., 1955-1963 (Box 19)
  - Peterson, E.E., 1952-1958 (Box 19)
  - Peterson, Frederick A., 1951-1975 (Box 19)
  - Phelps, David S., 1964-1975 (Box 19)
  - Phillips, Howard, 1962-1975 (Box 19)
  - Phillips, Philip, 1937-1973; 4 folders (Box 19)
  - Piggott, Stuart, 1953-1965 (Box 19)
  - Pilling, Arnold R., 1957-1970 (Box 19)
  - Pino, Lewis N., 1964-1965 (Box 19)
  - Pires-Ferreira, Jane Wheeler, 1972-1975 (Box 19)
  - Platt, Colin, 1967-1970 (Box 19)
  - Pollock, H.E.D., 1951-1954 (Box 19)
  - Porter, James, 1963-1975 (Box 19)
  - Powell, B. Bruce, 1960-1969 (Box 19)
  - Powell, Herbert F., 1935-1945 (Box 19)
  - Powell, L.H., 1953 (Box 19)
  - Prahl, Earl, 1967-1972 (Box 19)
  - Pratt, Peter P., 1952-1973 (Box 19)
  - Praus, Alexis A., 1947-1964 (Box 20)
  - Prescott, Kenneth W., 1955-1959 (Box 20)
  - Price, Carol, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Price, Douglas, 1968-1972 (Box 20)
  - Price, James E., 1967-1975; 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Printup, Dan, 1960-1974 (Box 20)
  - Prufer, Olaf H., 1960-1975 (Box 20)
  - Purchasing Department, 1948-1959 (Box 20)
  - Pa -- Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Pe -- Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Pf to Pi -- Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Pl to Po -- Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Po to Pu -- Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Quimby, George I., 1938-1975; 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Quimby, Thomas, 1957-1960 (Box 20)
  - Q -- Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Rackerby, Frank, 1969-1975 (Box 20)
  - Rackham Graduate School, 1946-1964 (Box 20)
  - Radiocarbon, 1965-1971 (Box 20)
  - Rainey, Froelich, 1940-1974 (Box 20)
  - Ralph, Elizabeth K., 1952-1974 (Box 20)
  - Rands, Robert L., 1952-1966 (Box 20)
  - Reagor, Simone, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Redfield, Robert, 1947-1950 (Box 20)
  - Reed, Charles A., 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - Reed, Erik K., 1947-1963 (Box 20)
  - Reed, Nelson A., 1964-1971 (Box 20)
  - Reeves, Dache M., 1941-1947 (Box 20)
  - Reichel-Dolmatoff, Gerardo, 1947-1965 (Box 20)
  - Reid, Russell, 1942-1955 (Box 20)
  - Reimann, Irving G., 1949-1969 (Box 20)
  - Reiter, Paul, 1947-1952 (Box 20)
  - Renfrew, A. Colin, 1967-1974 (Box 20)
  - Rex Gonzlez, Alberto, 1950-1974 (Box 20)
  - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1971-1975 (Box 20)
  - Rice, Warner G., 1945-1949 (Box 21)
  - Richmond, Gerald M., 1953-1969 (Box 21)
  - Ridley, Frank, 1950-1969 (Box 21)
  - Riley, Carroll L., 1958-1975 (Box 21)
  - Rinaldo, John B., 1949-1963 (Box 21)
  - Ritchie, William A., 1933-1972; 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Ritzenthaler, Robert, 1945-1975 (Box 21)
  - Robbins, Frank E., 1944-1952 (Box 21)
  - Robbins, Louise M., 1969-1974 (Box 21)
  - Robbins, Maurice, 1944-1967 (Box 21)
  - Roberts, Frank H.H. Jr., 1946-1961 (Box 21)
  - Rodabaugh, James H., 1947-1965 (Box 21)
  - Rodeck, Hugo G., 1949-1967 (Box 21)
  - Rogers, Edward S., 1965-1968 (Box 21)
  - Rolingson, Martha A., 1963-1968 (Box 21)
  - Ronen, Abraham, 1968-1971 (Box 21)
  - Roosa, William B., 1956-1975 (Box 21)
  - Root, William C., 1950-1958 (Box 21)
  - Roszell, O.E. (Plant Dept.), 1947-1949 (Box 21)
  - Rouse, Irving, 1941-1975; 5 folders (Box 21)
  - Rowe, Chandler W., 1950-1961 (Box 21)
  - Rowe, John H., 1950-1965 (Box 21)
  - Rubn de la Borbolla, Daniel, 1943-1959 (Box 21)
  - Ruppe, Reynold J., 1953-1969 (Box 21)
  - Ruyle, John B., 1942-1950 (Box 21)
  - Ruz, Alberto, 1953-1955 (Box 21)
  - Ra -- Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - Re to Rh -- Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - Ri to Ro -- Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Ro -- Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Ru -- Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Salter, L.J., 1956-1960 (Box 22)
  - Salzer, Robert J., 1961-1975 (Box 22)
  - Sanders, William T., 1959-1973 (Box 22)
  - Sanger, David, 1968-1970 (Box 22)
  - Sangines, Carlos Ponce, 1957-1966 (Box 22)
  - Sargent, Howard R., 1950-1975 (Box 22)
  - Satterthwaite, Linton, 1947-1959 (Box 22)
  - Sawyer, Charles H., 1957-1972 (Box 22)
  - Sawyer, Ralph A. (Dean of Graduate School), 1947-1964 (Box 22)
  - Sayles, E.B., 1937-1952 (Box 22)
  - Schaedel, Richard P., 1956-1966 (Box 22)
  - Schaeffer, Claude, 1940-1947 (Box 22)
  - Schmertz, Kennedy B., 1969-1974 (Box 22)
  - Schmitt, Karl, 1946-1952 (Box 22)
  - Schoenbeck, Ethel, 1940-1948 (Box 22)
  - Schoenwetter, James, 1961-1975 (Box 22)
  - Schorger, William D., 1967-1974 (Box 22)
  - Schreuder, Yda, 1972-1973 (Box 22)
  - Schroeder, Albert, 1950-1955 (Box 22)
  - Schroeder, David L., 1965-1968 (Box 22)
  - Schuster, Carl, 1956-1964 (Box 22)
  - Schwartz, Douglas W., 1956-1974 (Box 22)
  - Scollar, Irwin, 1964-1974 (Box 22)
  - Scott, Donald, 1936-1953 (Box 22)
  - Scully, Edward and Jeanne, 1949-1958 (Box 22)
  - Sears, William H., 1947-1975; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Sebeok, Thomas A., 1948-1958 (Box 22)
  - Seeman, Mark F., 1974-1975 (Box 22)
  - Selective Service, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Service, Elman, 1953-1974 (Box 22)
  - Setzler, Frank M., 1933-1964; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Shalkop, Robert L., 1952-1961 (Box 22)
  - Shane, Orrin C., III, 1965-1975 (Box 22)
  - Shapiro, Harry L., 1945-1970 (Box 22)
  - Shaw, Thurston, 1956-1975 (Box 22)
  - Shay, Creighton T., 1961-1967 (Box 22)
  - Shearer, James II, 1952 (Box 22)
  - Shepard, Anna O., 1946-1957 (Box 22)
  - Sheepard, Mary, 1953-1954 (Box 22)
  - Shetrone, H.C., 1946-1948 (Box 22)
  - Shimkin, Demitri B., 1956-1962 (Box 22)
  - Shippee, J. Mett, 1956-1968 (Box 22)
  - Shutler, Richard, 1959-1973 (Box 22)
  - Simpson, A.M., 1939-1944 (Box 22)
  - Sleight, Frederick W., 1941-1964 (Box 22)
  - Smail, William, 1951 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Allan F., 1966-1973 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Allan H., 1952-1968 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Arthur G., 1949-1964 (Box 22)
  - Smith, Bruce D., 1970-1975 (Box 23)
  - Smith, Carlyle S., 1944-1975 (Box 23)
  - Smith, Gerald P., 1963-1971 (Box 23)
  - Smith, Hale G., 1942-1973; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Smith, Marian W., 1947-1952 (Box 23)
  - Smith, Robert Eliot, 1944-1956 (Box 23)
  - Snow, Charles E., 1940-1958 (Box 23)
  - Sociedad Mexicana de Antropologa, 1947-1975 (Box 23)
  - Solecki, Ralph, 1948-1974 (Box 23)
  - Solheim, Wilhelm G., 1956-1973 (Box 23)
  - Soop, Everett J., 1945-1975 (Box 23)
  - South, Stanley, 1957-1966 (Box 23)
  - Spaulding, Albert C., 1937-1975; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Speck, Frank J., 1937-1946 (Box 23)
  - Speth, John D., 1968-1970 (Box 23)
  - Spier, Leslie, 1937-1951 (Box 23)
  - Spoehr, Alexander, 1940-1952 (Box 23)
  - Spotts, Julian C., 1950-1954 (Box 23)
  - Springer, James H., 1967-1973 (Box 23)
  - Spuhler, J.N., 1947-1968 (Box 23)
  - Spurr, Stephen H., 1956-1971 (Box 23)
  - Squier, Robert J., 1953-1965 (Box 23)
  - Starr, Frederick, 1960-1963 (Box 23)
  - Starr, Kenneth, 1959-1974 (Box 23)
  - Steegman, A. Theodore, 1960-1966 (Box 23)
  - Steele, John, 1945-1947 (Box 23)
  - Stein, William W., 1966-1968 (Box 23)
  - Stephenson, Robert L., 1949-1973; 4 folders (Box 23)
  - Steward, Julian, 1944-1952 (Box 23)
  - Stewart, Omer C., 1956-1958 (Box 23)
  - Stewart, Paul S., 1951 (Box 23)
  - Stewart, T.D., 1943-1974 (Box 23)
  - Stiles, William F., 1962-1965 (Box 23)
  - Stirling, M.W., 1936-1963 (Box 23)
  - Stokes, P.H., 1952-1957 (Box 23)
  - Stoltman, James B., 1966-1975 (Box 23)
  - Stone, Lyle M., 1969-1974 (Box 23)
  - Stothers, David M., 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - Stout, David Bond, 1937-1964 (Box 23)
  - Straus, Lawrence G., 1972-1975 (Box 23)
  - Stroebel, Ralph, 1958-1964 (Box 23)
  - Strong, W. Duncan, 1935-1952 (Box 23)
  - Struever, Stuart, 1952-1975; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Stubbs, Stanley, 1952-1956 (Box 23)
  - Sturtevant, William C., 1935-1973 (Box 23)
  - Sugihara, Sosuke, 1957-1975 (Box 23)
  - Sulimirski, T., 1954-1968 (Box 24)
  - Sussman, Alfred S., 1969-1971 (Box 24)
  - Swanson, Earl H., 1957-1975 (Box 24)
  - Swanton, John R., 1935-1939 (Box 24)
  - Swartz, B.K., 1965-1975 (Box 24)
  - Swartz, Carl E., 1965-1968 (Box 24)
  - Swauger, James L., 1949-1975 (Box 24)
  - Sweet, Louise E., 1955-1974 (Box 24)
  - Sa -- Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - Sc -- Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - Se to Sh -- Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - Sh to Sl -- Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - Sm -- Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - Sn to Sr -- Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - St -- Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Su to Sy -- Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - Tax, Sol, 1945-1972 (Box 24)
  - Taylor, Dee C., 1954-1974 (Box 24)
  - Taylor, R.E., 1972-1974 (Box 24)
  - Taylor, Walter W., 1945-1959 (Box 24)
  - Taylor, William E., 1952-1975 (Box 24)
  - Teocentli, 1951-1970 (Box 24)
  - Terrell, John, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Thieme, Fred P., 1949-1971 (Box 24)
  - Thomas, Ronald A., 1967-1975 (Box 24)
  - Thomas, William W., 1954-1955 (Box 24)
  - Thompson, Harold W., 1967-1975 (Box 24)
  - Thompson, J. Eric, 1947-1950 (Box 24)
  - Thompson, Milton D., 1967-1973 (Box 24)
  - Thompson, Raymond H., 1952-1968 (Box 24)
  - Thorne, Robert M., 1965-1967 (Box 24)
  - Thuma, Burton D., 1951-1964 (Box 24)
  - Thurman, Melburn D., 1972-1974 (Box 24)
  - Titiev, Mischa, 1949-1955 (Box 24)
  - Titterington, Paul F., 1936-1969; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Tolstoy, Paul, 1957-1974 (Box 25)
  - Tompkins, C.E., 1948-1954 (Box 25)
  - Tong, Marvin E., 1950-1972 (Box 25)
  - Toth, Alan, 1971-1975 (Box 25)
  - Towne, Claude, 1949-1951 (Box 25)
  - Townsend, Earl C., 1953-1972 (Box 25)
  - Trager, George L., 1961 (Box 25)
  - Treganza, Adan E., 1955-1968 (Box 25)
  - Tremer, Carl E., 1948-1950 (Box 25)
  - Trickey, E. Bruce, 1955-1961 (Box 25)
  - Trigger, Bruce G., 1972-1974 (Box 25)
  - Trowbridge, Harry M., 1940-1963 (Box 25)
  - Tuck, James A., 1969-1973 (Box 25)
  - Turner, Gordon B., 1968-1974 (Box 25)
  - Ta to Th -- Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - Th to Tl -- Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - To Ty -- Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - U -- Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - Van Doorslaer, Marguerite P., 1955-1966 (Box 25)
  - Van Zeist, Willem, 1961 (Box 25)
  - Vescelius, Gary S., 1948-72 (Box 25)
  - Vickery, Kent, 1969-1975 (Box 25)
  - Voegelin, Carl and Erminie, 1937-1971 (Box 25)
  - V -- Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Wachtel, H.C., 1952-1954 (Box 25)
  - Wadlow, Walter, 1950-1952 (Box 25)
  - Walker, Edwin F., 1940-1952 (Box 25)
  - Wallace, Anthony F.C., 1947-1969 (Box 25)
  - Wallace, David D., 1967-1968 (Box 25)
  - Walter, Erich A., 1955-1965 (Box 25)
  - Walthall, John A., 1969-1974 (Box 25)
  - Ward, Lauriston, 1951-1958 (Box 25)
  - Waring, Antonio J., 1947-1963 (Box 25)
  - Washburn, S.L., 1947-1953 (Box 25)
  - Wassen, S. Henry, 1948-1965 (Box 25)
  - Waterbolk, H.T., 1965-1972 (Box 25)
  - Watkins, Herbert G. (Secretary of the University), 1948-1958 (Box 25)
  - Watson, James B. and Virginia, 1946-1959 (Box 25)
  - Watson, Patty Jo, 1964-1975 (Box 26)
  - Wauchope, Robert, 1940-1964 (Box 26)
  - Webb, Clarence H., 1940-1975 (Box 26)
  - Webb, Malcolm C., 1959-1974 (Box 26)
  - Webb, William S., 1933-1955; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Webber, Howard R., 1966-1968 (Box 26)
  - Weber, Ronald L., 1970-1972 (Box 26)
  - Wedel, Waldo R., 1937-1967 (Box 26)
  - Weeks, I.D., 1948-1949 (Box 26)
  - Weer, Paul, 1934-1955 (Box 26)
  - Weinberg, Gladys D., 1963 (Box 26)
  - Welles, C. Bradford, 1947-1948 (Box 26)
  - Wendorf, Fred, 1946-1975 (Box 26)
  - Wenley, A.G., 1951-1959 (Box 26)
  - Wetherington, Ronald K., 1958-1975 (Box 26)
  - Wetmore, Alexander, 1936-1943 (Box 26)
  - Whallon, Robert, 1966-1974 (Box 26)
  - Wheat, Joe Ben, 1948-1972 (Box 26)
  - Wheeler, Richard P., 1952-1967 (Box 26)
  - Whitaker, Arthur P., 1955-1957 (Box 26)
  - White, Anta M., 1962-1968 (Box 26)
  - White, Leslie A., 1946-1970 (Box 26)
  - White, Marian E., 1951-1975 (Box 26)
  - Whiteford, Andrew H., 1939-1961 (Box 26)
  - Whitehead, Donald R., 1965 (Box 26)
  - Whitehead, Kenneth D., 1970-1971 (Box 26)
  - Whitmer, Charles A., 1960-1963 (Box 26)
  - Wilbur, C. Martin, 1936-1940 (Box 26)
  - Wilder, Charles, 1935-1951 (Box 26)
  - Wilding-White, Fred, 1961 (Box 26)
  - Wilford, Lloyd A., 1941-1958 (Box 26)
  - Wilkinson, Richard G., 1969-1975 (Box 26)
  - Will, George F.
    - Correspondence, 1942-1950 (Box 26)
    - SAA Business, 1951-1953 (Box 26)
  - Willets, Jane, 1947-1949 (Box 26)
  - Willey, Gordon R., 1940-1975; 3 folders (Box 26)
  - Williams, G. Mennen, 1969-1975 (Box 26)
  - Williams, Ray, 1966-1972 (Box 26)
  - Williams, Robert L., 1947-1955 (Box 26)
  - Williams, Stephen, 1950-1975; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Wilmeth, Roscoe H., 1953-1975 (Box 27)
  - Wilmsen, Edwin N., 1960-1974 (Box 27)
  - Wilson, John T., 1963-1965 (Box 27)
  - Wimberley, Stephen B. and Christine, 1948-1975 (Box 27)
  - Wintemberg, W.J., 1938-1939 (Box 27)
  - Winter, Marcus, 1972-1974 (Box 27)
  - Winters, Howard D., 1955-1975 (Box 27)
  - Withers, Arnold, 1952-1964 (Box 27)
  - Witt, Arthur, 1957-1958 (Box 27)
  - Witteborg, Lothar P., 1949-1956 (Box 27)
  - Witthoft, John, 1946-1972 (Box 27)
  - Wittry, Warren L., 1952-1971 (Box 27)
  - Wobst, H. Martin, 1966-1972 (Box 27)
  - Wolf, Eric, 1969-1971 (Box 27)
  - Wood, Leonard G., 1950-1954 (Box 27)
  - Wood, W. Raymond, 1956-1973 (Box 27)
  - Woodbury, Richard B. and Nathalie, 1941-1975 (Box 27)
  - Woodcock, William E., 1972-1975 (Box 27)
  - Woolworth, Alan R., 1960-1970 (Box 27)
  - Work, R.W., 1959-1963 (Box 27)
  - Wormington, H. Marie, 1949-1973 (Box 27)
  - Wortner, Stanley, 1950-1972 (Box 27)
  - Wray, Charles F., 1941-1973 (Box 27)
  - Wray, Donald, 1941-1958 (Box 27)
  - Wright, Gary A., 1964-1969 (Box 27)
  - Wright, Gordon K., 1961-1963 (Box 27)
  - Wright, Harry N., 1950 (Box 27)
  - Wright, Henry T., 1967-1975 (Box 27)
  - Wright, Herbert E., 1957-1973 (Box 27)
  - Wright, James V., 1957-1970 (Box 27)
  - Wright, Ross Pier, 1934-1958 (Box 27)
  - Wyckoff, Don G., 1967-1971 (Box 27)
  - Wa -- Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - We -- Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Wh to Wi -- Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Wi -- Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Wo to Wy -- Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - X -- Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Yaggie, Ida, 1968-1972 (Box 27)
  - Yarnell, Richard A., 1962-1970 (Box 27)
  - Yengoyan, Aram A., 1972-1975 (Box 27)
  - Young, John R., 1948 (Box 27)
  - Y -- Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Zavala, Silvio, 1953-1961 (Box 27)
  - Zepp, Erwin C., 1948-1959 (Box 27)
  - Zumberge, James H., 1955-1972 (Box 27)
  - Z -- Miscellaneous (Box 27)
- Correspondence, 1975-1997
  The Correspondence, 1975-1997 series (6 linear feet) contains incoming and some outgoing personal and professional correspondence from the years following Griffin's official retirement from the Museum of Anthropology. The series employs the same alphabetical arrangement as the Correspondence, 1930-1975 series, but is maintained separately because of the differing nature of its content and context of creation. There is significant overlap between the correspondents in both correspondence series; in most cases, the researcher interested in seeing a comprehensive record of correspondence with a particular person should consult both series.